I'll go give this red string
to my sister Xingyao later,
and say goodbye to her.
Your sister is an ominous person.
How can you see her before your wedding?
Xingyao.
Why are you locked up here?
Aren't you
already dead?
How are you still alive?
I didn't
kill you.
It wasn't me.
It was the Eldest Princess.
What exactly
is going on?
It was the Eldest Princess.
She said
she'd help me kill you
and let me take your place as the Empress.
She said
she could help me remove my birthmark,
and then give me back my freedom.
In that case,
because the original Cangyue was already dead,
I accidentally came to this world.
But,
after I came to Donglin,
she said,
she said my resentment was too deep,
perfect for raising the most poisonous Gu.
So I was locked up here.
Resentment.
So you hated
my parents to the bone,
so much that you'd sacrifice
the lives of our entire clan?
What are you talking about?
What lives of the entire clan?
They are all dead.
As far as the eye could see,
corpses littered the fields.
How is that possible?
How could this be?
I didn't mean it.
I really didn't mean it.
Since I am the one
who caused all this...
Then let me
end this.
Xingyao, what are you doing?
Don't do anything stupid.
There must be another way to solve this.
Xingyao!
Sister!
The Jiuyin Gu is refined with human blood.
They are born as a mother-child pair.
The mother and child Gu are placed in two people's bodies.
The child Gu absorbs life essence
to supply the mother Gu to release venom.
The only solution
is to take the child Gu.
The host of the child Gu must be killed.
Otherwise,
they will never die
or perish.
Xingyao,
don't be impulsive.
There must be another way.
Let me get you out first, Xingyao.
Only if I die,
can the others infected with the Gu
continue to live.
Sister,
I'm sorry.
Xingyao!
Experiencer's character objective 80% complete.
Xingyao said that in three days at most,
the Gu poison in your body will be cleared.
Grand General Pixiu,
charge!
Yan,
how can Pixiu still go to battle?
Even Sleeping Beauty can slay demons.
So Pixiu can go to battle too.
Look, there's also this.
A tiger tally.
Yan, where did this come from?
This is a new gift from my brother.
My brother said
that with this, I can deploy troops
and go into battle.
When did His Majesty give it to you?
Before my brother went to sleep.
It seems Si Xingxuan also noticed something was wrong.
He kept a trick up his sleeve before fainting.
He isn't stupid enough to be easily brought down by Si Xinglan.
I didn't expect the Eldest Princess to have poisoned me so long ago.
No wonder I've been extremely irritable at times over the years.
I thought I really was a tyrant.